# **Artem Sheveley**

## **Full Stack Developer**

Central Israel | 058-507-0892 | artem6evelev92@gmail.com Github | LinkedIn | Personal Website

#### **SUMMARY**

Junior Full-Stack Developer with a background in Business Development, Planning and Analysis. Experienced in JavaScript, React, Node.js. Possess strong skills in analyzing and solving complex problems that have helped the company provide excellent tools to every management team that I've

I know how to meet deadlines, work under pressure and handle multiple tasks. I am ready to quickly adapt to new situations and discover some interesting new fields.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Programming Languages: JavaScript (ES6)

Front-End: React.js, Redux, jQuery, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS

Back-End: PostgreSQL, SQL, Node.js

Software: Figma, Git, Github

#### **TECHNICAL PROJECTS**

# Telegram Bot - Github

This bot uses SQLite database to store data, user can create their own database of products, clients, etc.

- Use node is package for database connection with SQLite
- Execute SQL commands synchronously and asynchronously

### RESTful API - Github

Build a fully functional REST API

- Setup a Node.js server with Express and connect server to MongoDB through Mongoose
- Setup REST API with MongoDB and Node.js

#### Book Keeper - Github | Demo

Allow users to save bookmarks and click on the links to go to those Websites

- Store data in a local storage as a result user can use it anytime.
- All bookmarks are clickable with favicons

#### Movie App - Github | Demo

A Movie App where user can find film and check rating and description of it

- Create search functionality
- Add Javascript to make fetch request to get a data to show the most popular movies

# **EXPERIENCE**

# **China Market Tour Operator**

Tel-Aviv. Israel

Naftali Tours

March 2019 - Present

- Create a budget for incoming groups from China
- Establish business connections with Chinese travel companies, as a result per week 8-12 groups from China came to Israel
- Translate contracts from Chinese to English, as a result more than 10 signed contracts per year

CEO

Ideal International Kindergarten

Harbin, China November 2016 - May 2018

- Developed teaching methodology for Chinese children
- Lectured about the methodology in other schools and kindergartens
- Managed Chinese and foreign teachers

## **EDUCATION**

## **Full Stack Web Development**

Tel-Aviv, Israel

Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp

April 2021 - June 2021

# The Complete Web Developer in 2021: Zero to Mastery by Andrei Neagoie

**Udemy Course** September 2020 - December 2020

# The Complete 2021 Web Development Bootcamp by Angela Yu

May 2020 - August 2020 **Udemy Course** 

# **Bachelor Degree, International Trade and Economics**

Harbin, China September 2011 - June 2016 Heilongjiang University

### **LANGUAGES**

English - fluent Chinese - fluent Hebrew - advanced Russian - native